topsite.com 2018-12-02

# TopSite - Privacy Policy

## We respect your privacy because we treasure ours

TopSite.com (the "Site") is a website owned and operated by SimilarGroup ("SimilarGroup", "We" or "Us") We treasure our privacy and that’s exactly why we made every effort to create a service that would live up to user privacy standards we would be comfortable with. 

## User Consent

When you use this site and its services you consent to collection, use and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy statement. 

SimilarWeb knows that you care how information about you is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by US when you make use of the Site and software. (the “Software”) and how the information will be used. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. 

This Policy may be updated from time to time and therefore we ask you to check back periodically the most updated form of Policy as indicated below. Your continued use of the Products and this Site after this Policy has been amended and the "Last Updated" date has been modified, shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms of this Policy, as amended. 

## Information that we collect

Information collected online can generally be categorized as either non-personal information or personally identifiable information. Non-personal information is information that cannot by itself be traced back to a specific individual. For example, we know how many search queries we receive each day but we do not know the names and email addresses of the persons submitting the queries. 

We respect and protect the privacy of our users and take appropriate steps to safeguard your personal information. The use of this website and its related software, upgrades or updates and all related services and special offers (the "Product") are subject to the here under provisions of this Policy. 

## Information you give us

Currently, we don’t ask you to register for TopSite.com because we simply don’t need you to. When you send email or make a vote in our Software, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

## Automatic Tracking

Our server automatically collects additional information about your use of our website (navigational data). Navigational data includes the type of browser you are using, your IP address, the URL you have come from and the time spent at that URL, cookies and your domain type and server. This kind of information is collected by many sites and used to monitor use of the relevant site. 

If you use our Software, it will contact our servers periodically or in response to certain actions you take in your browser. Each of those contacts generates the same kind of information generated when you visit our website, as described above. Additionally, the Software will transmit whatever data is necessary to provide particular features of the Software and to monitor their use. 

Our Software will be able to and may track certain information including online navigational information about you and your correspondence in order to perform internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior. This non-personal information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Non-personally identifiable information may be analyzed by us for the purpose of improving and expanding the functionality of our Product. In addition, the Product checks regularly for product update on our servers and download such updates when needed. 

## Disclosure of Users’ Data to Third Parties

We may disclose your information and navigational data in aggregated form to potential and actual advertisers, sponsors, investors, partners, consultants and advisers. This information and data which we supply will not be identified as your personal information. We reserve the right to use and disclose non-personal Information to third parties in our discretion. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. 

For example, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on the FreshPatents.com website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to FreshContext LLC sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy: <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Otherwise, we do not disclose personal information, such as your email address, unless we are required to do so by law, regulation, an applicable industry code, for safety reasons or where we reasonably believe that you are in breach of the terms and conditions of use of the Site or are engaged in illegal activities. 

## Links and Displayed Sites

As part of our core functionality, the Product may discover and recommend content that the Product determines may be of interest to you. We do not have control over third-party websites or their information collection practices and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such linked or otherwise displayed sites. 

## Disclosure of Personal Information 

We may share some or all of your personal information with any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control we have or may have in the future (collectively, "Affiliates").In which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. 

## Disclosure of Information in the Event of a Merge

We may merge or be acquired by another business entity or may sell all or substantially all of our assets to an acquirer. In the event of such merger, acquisition or sale, We may share some or all or your personally identifiable information with the acquiring company in order to continue serving you. In such event and if applicable, We will provide notice that such information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at 

**Last updated – November 12, 2009**
